In this clip we're going to talk about how to clean a trophy.
And basically what we're going to use, we got a little trophy here, that's got a little dust on it, it's been sitting on the shelf for a while.
Actually there are more ways not to clean a trophy than there are to clean a trophy.
What we're going to use is just your basic household paper towel.
And we're going to use a cleaning solution which is basically your average window cleaner.
We try not to use anything with any alcohol or any solvent in it.
And we don't want to spray it directly onto to trophy, we want to spray it onto our cloth and then just very gently wipe off the dust.
There's not much on here but the important thing is not to use any harsh solvent and just wipe the dust off gently.
And that's all there is to that.
Certain types of trophies are going to require, of course a little bit more special care, such as this cup with a solid walnut base.
Now the walnut itself is going to get a little dusty and you might want to use just some ordinary household furniture polish which you can find anywhere.
And just apply a little bit to your, again we use a paper towel, you can use a soft cloth if you wish and just a little bit of the furniture polish, not very much.
Then just very gently wipe the dust off and rub the furniture polish into the wood, and it will give it a nice shine and look as good as new.